I was just in Florida I was in St
Augustine Florida which by the way I
don't know if you know this or Not St
Augustine Florida is the oldest city um
in the United States you can go there
and see all the buildings that they
built way back in the 1500s and uh then
you can go to Tampa and you can actually
meet the people that built
them then you can drive down to Naples
and meet their
parents there's a lot of old people in
Florida I was at a Walmart the reader
said can I get you a
basket I don't know can
you
clear can I get you a
casket no it's a super center you know
they sell
them and listen I'm not talking old like
80 or 90 my mother and and father of
that age I'm talking people in their
late 100s early 200s I mean they would
come to my shows like this and stare at
me like the Amish at Best
Buy I've never actually seen dead people
sit
up the very first time I was ever down
in Florida I was in Miami beautiful city
by the way Miami Florida and I'm playing
golf with a friend of mine who grew up
in the State of Florida on the golf
course with us and apparently this is
very popular is an alligator and I'm
freaking out and my friend he doesn't
even Flinch he just looks at me and goes
you know R want to hear the rest of the
joke click the play button to continue
watching